Review the InstallStep.txt file to learn how to install the driver.

Step by step
1. Extract the drivers package and get into the folder
2. Click the File option from the upper left corner of the driver package folder
3. Move the cursor to the Open Windows PowerShell option
4. Select Open Windows PowerShell as administrator option
5. Select Yes, Allow this app to make changes to your device.
6. Input .\Setup.bat
7. Press Enter key to start drivers installation until return to next command line.
8. After install successfully, please restart.
